<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Terms and Policies on DANDI</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/dandi-hugo-example/docs/08_terms_policies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Terms and Policies on DANDI</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/dandi-hugo-example/docs/08_terms_policies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Use v1.0.1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/dandi-hugo-example/docs/08_terms_policies/00_terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/dandi-hugo-example/docs/08_terms_policies/00_terms/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The DANDI data archive (&amp;ldquo;DANDI&amp;rdquo;) is offered by the DANDI project as part of its&#xA;mission to make available the results of its work.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Use of DANDI, both the uploading and downloading of data, denotes agreement with&#xA;the following terms:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;DANDI is an open dissemination research data repository for the preservation&#xA;and making available of research, educational and informational content. Access&#xA;to DANDI’s content is open to all.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Content may be uploaded free of charge by the US BRAIN Initiative and other&#xA;projects required to submit data to a public archive and those without ready&#xA;access to an organized data center.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General Policies v1.1.0</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/dandi-hugo-example/docs/08_terms_policies/01_policies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/dandi-hugo-example/docs/08_terms_policies/01_policies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;Content&lt;a class=&#34;td-heading-self-link&#34; href=&#34;#content&#34; aria-label=&#34;Heading self-link&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scope:&lt;/strong&gt; Neurophysiology research. Raw and derived experimental data. Content&#xA;must not violate privacy or copyright, or breach confidentiality or non-disclosure&#xA;agreements for data collected from human subjects.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Status of research data:&lt;/strong&gt; Empirical (not simulated) data and associated metadata from any stage of the&#xA;research study&amp;rsquo;s life cycle is accepted.  Simulated data is handled on a case-by-case basis, contact the DANDI team&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eligible users:&lt;/strong&gt; Anyone working with the data in the scope of the archive may register as a user of DANDI. All users are&#xA;allowed to deposit content for which they possess the appropriate rights&#xA;and which falls within the &lt;strong&gt;scope&lt;/strong&gt; of the archive.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ownership:&lt;/strong&gt; By uploading content, no change of ownership is implied and no&#xA;property rights are transferred to the DANDI team. All uploaded content remains&#xA;the property of the parties prior to submission and must be accompanied by a license allowing&#xA;DANDI project data access, archival, and re-distribution (see &lt;strong&gt;License&lt;/strong&gt; below).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data file formats:&lt;/strong&gt; DANDI only accepts data using standardized formats such&#xA;as &lt;a href=&#34;https://nwb.org&#34;&gt;Neurodata Without Borders&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://bids.neuroimaging.io/&#34;&gt;Brain Imaging Data Structure&lt;/a&gt;,&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;NIDM&#34;&gt;Neuroimaging Data Model&lt;/a&gt;, and other &lt;a href=&#34;https://braininitiative.nih.gov/&#34;&gt;BRAIN Initiative&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;standards. We are working with the community to improve these standards and to&#xA;make DANDI archive FAIR.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data quality:&lt;/strong&gt; All data are provided “as-is”, and the user shall hold&#xA;DANDI and data providers supplying data to the DANDI Archive free and harmless in&#xA;connection with the use of such data.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Metadata types and sources:&lt;/strong&gt; All metadata is stored internally in JSON format&#xA;according to a defined JSON schema. Metadata records violating the schema are not allowed.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language:&lt;/strong&gt; Textual items must be in English. Latin names could be used in exceptional cases where appropriate.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Licenses:&lt;/strong&gt; Users must specify a license for each dataset chosen from the list of the DANDI archive approved licenses. Users allow for the DANDI archive to extract metadata records and make them available under permissive CC0 license.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;access-and-reuse&#34;&gt;Access and Reuse&lt;a class=&#34;td-heading-self-link&#34; href=&#34;#access-and-reuse&#34; aria-label=&#34;Heading self-link&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Access to data objects:&lt;/strong&gt; Files deposited to the archive are accessible to the public&#xA;openly or accessible to collaborators for embargoed datasets. Access to metadata and data&#xA;files is provided over standard protocols such as HTTPS.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
